The war ended, and peace was established
between the kingdom and principality.
Other nations had taken advantage
of the war to invade,
which demanded the kingdom's attention.
But the principality itself was no more.
House Fanoss rejoined
the kingdom as a duchy.
On top of exorbitant reparations,
the kingdom was pushing for an
unfair and humiliating treaty.
Lady Mylene.
Meanwhile, all the attention
I was receiving from ladies
put me in high spirits, but...
Viscount Bartfort.
I have a personal request.
Please don't, Lady Mylene!
What's gotten into you?
Please save Julius and his friends.
What?
You guys really are stupid.
This World Is Really Tough for Mobs
Bartfort.
I don't want to be executed! Save me!
What did you expect?
That idiot attacked House Fanoss.
I just caused a little commotion.
I'm not marrying Hertrude to impose
an unfair treaty on the principality.
I'm nobody's tool.
As a result, the palace
completely lost face
and had to compromise on the treaty.
I never thought that idiot
prince would be my savior.
And you four went crazy at the temple.
We were only stopping Marie's execution!
After all, she's our Saint.
We have no regrets.
This is our code of chivalry!
In any case, you made enemies
of the palace and temple.
Accept your deaths.
No! Help me!
Are you insane?
You want me to spare them in exchange
for what you earned in the war?
Yes. If that's not enough,
then I'll pay out of my own coffers.
Please spare them.
What should I do?
Look at this bastard putting on airs.
Milord, why go this far for them?
Because I'm stuck with them, I guess.
Besides, I'd originally intended to
live a relaxed life as a baronet.
I'll take this opportunity to start over.
I see. They've gained a good friend.
Your Highness, may I take it from here?
Very well.
Great, but now I'm basically retired.
It's the start of my new NPC life.
Also, about Angelica...
Don't do it, Bartfort!
Have you gone mad?!
Shut up! Marie, your blood
will stain Murasamekai!
Wh-Why do you have that rare item?
I thought you were saving me from death!
I heard you made Angie and Livia grovel!
That was, uh...
Angie was shamed for tarnishing
her family's name,
and both she and Livia were hurt.
So you have to die! I'll kill you!
Stop! I won't let you
lay a finger on Marie!
Shut up! Kill her, Luxion!
Are you sure?
Kill her!
In that case, pardon me.
Me, too?
Have you calmed down some?
We have to live on a floating
island in your territory?
Yeah. You're to live a
self-sufficient life there.
You're being exiled.
What? Absolutely not.
Don't complain after I saved your neck!
Or are you that desperate
to lose your head?
B-But I'm a city girl, you know?
I bet you're planning to build
another harem in the capital!
Don't forget you were a hag with
a kid in your previous life!
Oh, shut up! You've got the villainess
and protagonist serving you!
Our relationship is pure, thank you!
We're not like you!
You're just a wimp!
It's your fault I died!
Luxion, say something!
Yes, Master.
I feel very sorry for your previous
parents who had you two as children.
Also, Marie is right. Perhaps it's
time you made a decision, Master.
What are you talking about?
The two of them have just arrived.
Huh?
Mr. Leon.
Leon.
We need to talk.
Do you have a minute?
Wh-What'd you want to talk about?
Leon, I love you.
At some point, I started thinking
about you more than His Highness.
I enjoyed spending time with you.
I felt comfortable being around you.
I love you.
Wh-Why is she smiling?
What should I do?
Luxion, help...
Who are you?
Hi. It's me, Cleare.
Oh, you're the Vice's AI.
Hello again.
That voice...
You're the AI from the elven ruins!
I was transferred to this device.
I see. Wait, where's Luxion?
I asked that oaf to take a back seat.
They were happy to oblige.
That bastard abandoned me!
Mr. Leon.
Y-Yes?
I still love you.
I believe nobody's feelings
are stronger than mine.
I-I see.
What the hell am I saying?
So please give us your answer.
Me or Livia?
No, you don't have to choose either of us.
Just tell us how you feel.
How I feel?
I...
I love both of you... you... you...
My dad was promoted to upper sixth
rank for saving so many evacuees.
He's currently helping me repair
Arroganz and the Partner.
After being forsaken by my dad,
Zola's mansion in the capital
burned down during the war,
and her family was stripped of its
title for refusing to join the war.
In the capital, the attitude of female
superiority was beginning to change.
Meanwhile, I...
Viscount Leon Fou Bartfort,
you performed splendidly in the war.
I'm so sleepy. Please let this end.
You are relieved of your
duties as supreme commander.
Also, I'm promoting you to
count, lower third rank.
What?!
Your numerous achievements in
battle call for a suitable title.
A count as his age?
That's the highest title for non-royals.
He's more of an upstart than ever.
They look shocked, too.
This asshole made this decision
on his own to spite me!
This is what you get for
stealing the king's thunder.
If that is your wish, Your Majesty.
He's stealing my chance to shine.
I look forward to your
future exploits, Count.
S-Screw this jerk!
I'll get back at him someday!
You were promoted again?
Well, aren't you lucky?
Meanwhile, I've been exiled.
Shut up. You don't know how I feel.
Anyway, what'd you want to talk about?
I actually have some important
information about that otome game.
What?
You probably don't know since you
died after beating the first game,
but that otome game became a series.
What? That shitty game?
That's right. It wasn't popular at all,
but the devs were weirdly
passionate about it.
I-I don't believe it.
Additionally, only the land guardian
was the final boss of the first game.
The sky and sea guardians
appear in the third game.
Which means the first and third
games were blended together.
No wonder I didn't recognize them.
Wait. Does that mean...
Bingo. There's still the
boss of the second game.
This world isn't safe from danger yet.
No way!
Do you get it now?
I know things about the
game that you don't.
So let's make a deal.
What do you want?
Well, for starters...
Please give me an allowance!
What?
Carla and Kyle are fine, but those idiots
could never survive in the boonies!
They're no different from the useless
hobosexuals of my previous life!
Sparkle.
You really are a magnet for shitty guys.
Fine. You can have an allowance.
Thank you, Brother!
Whatever. Just tell me
about the second game.
Okay.
The second game is set in the Alzer
Republic instead of the kingdom.
The Alzer Republic?
Oh, that study abroad destination.
Apparently, the world is destroyed
unless the protagonist gets together
with a romantic interest
in the second game.
Seriously, give me a break.
You must be a worrywart if you're going
to study abroad in the Alzer Republic.
I don't have a choice.
I'm curious to see how the changes
to the first game affected it,
and we could be looking at trouble
if there's someone like Marie there.
You would've been quite popular
if you'd stayed in the kingdom.
Just how tough is this world for mobs?
Leon.
Dad.
Do you have a moment?
An engagement party?
Yeah. I'd like you to attend.
I underestimated my brother.
I didn't realize he'd made such
good progress at finding a spouse.
Yeah, I suppose.
I can still leave in time to study
abroad, so I'd be happy to attend.
Wait a minute. Something's not right.
Aren't you the man of the hour?
Why is my outfit flashier?
Well, you know... you're a count.
What? Luxion, doesn't
this seem strange to you?
Does it? I'm sure everyone's just nervous.
No, something's definitely off.
Wait. Could it be...
Did you trick me, old man?!
I did no such thing.
You simply misunderstood me.
Since you're so indecisive,
we made arrangements for you.
H-How could you?
Th-The room is full of important guests!
I can't run away!
Congratulations, milord.
I have a letter from His Majesty for you.
What? From the king?
I heard you've been running from marriage,
so I've done everything in my
power to move things along.
Welcome to the end of your life.
Sincerely, your talented
and wonderful king.
Damn it!
We're sorry for tricking you.
But you kept dodging the question.
Why'd you even fall for me?
Because you're you.
Leon, be my husband.
I fell in love with you
because you're you, Mr. Leon.
I'll never let you go.
Oh, fine. Do what you want.
It's not like I don't like them.
I love them.
I was tricked, but I don't
feel terrible about it.
Congratulations on your engagement.
That was a lovely ceremony.
Is that all you have to say,
you pieces of junk?
But tomorrow, I'm going to study abroad.
I didn't think I'd be living by myself
so soon after my engagement.
I'm not ready yet!
Peek.
What do you think we're here
to do? We just came to talk.
Peek.
Huh?
We haven't gotten a chance to
talk much. Is that all right?
Th-That's totally fine.
We wanted to thank you.
So much has happened since we met you.
You've always stuck by our sides.
You've helped us so much.
Angie, Livia...
I owe you guys.
I don't know what I would've
done without you.
Thank you. I owe Marie
and those guys, too.
You're right.
Leon, you'd better come back.
We'll be waiting for you.
I promise I will.
After that, we stayed up late talking.
It was torture.
Rauda, everyone's gone now.
Father, Mother. Even Vandel is gone.
If you leave me, I'll be all alone.
If only I'd been stronger.
I'm reminded of the elf chief's words.
Leon Fou Bartfort...
If you can find a way to walk together,
your difficult path will
be bathed in light,
and they shall be a reliable
source of support.
You're leaving now?
I feel sorry for you, Leon.
You're finally getting more
invitations from girls.
Meanwhile, we're being treated like
heroes for our evacuation efforts.
We're in our popular phase!
Popular phase! Popular phase!
Popular phase!
You'll pay for this.
Leon.
Ladies.
If you get sick of the Redgraves,
House Atlee is here for you.
House Roseblade's doors
are open to you, as well.
Actually, what if...
...we eloped right now?
Mr. Leon.
Master!
Seeing the outside world
will be a good experience.
As both a gentleman and a person,
may you deepen your code of
chivalry as you push forward.
Yes, Master.
Master, it's nearly time to depart.
I've procured a new ship
for you so that you won't
embarrass yourself as a
representative of the kingdom.
Whoa, it's awesome!
It's the Einhorn. I thought it
worthy of today's departure.
Yeah. Let's go.
You didn't need to see him off?
No. It'd only cause trouble
for him if we cried in public.
How admirable.
And there must be a reason he
suddenly decided to study abroad.
We plan to study really hard
so we can help him someday.
We need to grow so much that
he'll be surprised when he returns.
You're right.
Let's do our best.
Damn it!
That was a nice sendoff,
but I don't want to go abroad!
You just can't let it go, can you?
Anyway, you're not going to open this box?
It's apparently from the palace.
Oh, right. They did give me something.
Is it a gift for the Alzer Republic?
Why did you close it?!
What are you doing here?!
W-Well, you see...
Wh-What is this?
We got this for you.
We had it made by a reputable craftsman.
It was pretty expensive.
But we had our allowance from Bartfort.
He kept trying to make your
chest bigger. It was an ordeal.
Th-They didn't hesitate
to spend a fortune.
A whole year of living
expenses down the drain.
These worthless idiots!
The queen was furious when she found out.
It seems you need to learn
more about the world.
Go study abroad with Leon!
So the rest of them are here, too.
Aren't you excited, Your Highness?
Yeah.
Alzer, huh?
I'm happy anywhere,
as long as I'm with Marie.
I'll become a man worthy of her!
We're starting anew.
Yeah!
So we'll be spending more
time together, Brother.
You can't be serious!
Is this what they call beautiful
brotherly and sisterly love?
You two certainly are alike.
Shut up!
Damn it!
This shitty otome game!
This world is really tough for mobs!
Trapped in a Dating Sim 2
Supreme Commander
Miura Kazuya